Guide to the Tom Law San Francisco Bay Area Punk and Rock Handbill and Poster Collection M1976
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Posters, 3 manuscript boxes, 2 flat boxes and 1 large map folder
  - Folder 11, 1983- 1986 (Box 2)
    1. Miller The Killer; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-07-28; 8.5x11.
    2. The Cat Heads, The Whitefronts; Hotel Utah; 584 4th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-04; 11x17 [two 8.5x11s].
    3. Ice Nine, Fade to Black, Orange Curtain; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-25; 8.5x11.
    4. Life On Mars; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1984-01-06; 8.5x11.
    5. The Looters, Jump-5, Aquabops, DJ Raoul Thomas; Swedish American Hall; 2174 Market St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-12-29; 8.5x11.
    6. Lonnie Mack, Ron Thompson & The Resistors, Little John Chrisley, Hair Of The Dog; Wolfgang's; 901 Columbus Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-05; 8.5x11.
    7. The Looters, Burnt Offering, Dominique, Exocets; Club Foot; 2520 3rd St. San Francisco, CA; 1983-05-20; 8.5x11.
    8. Impulse F; The Oasis; 298 11th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-10-09; 8.5x11.
    9. Lifers, Fade to Black, Black Dolls, Men In Black; On Broadway; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1983-04-08; 8.5x11.
    10. Ludovico Teknique; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-10-20; 8.5x11.
    11. Big Loot (members of the Looters and Big City); 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-24; 8.5x11.
    12. Great Rock n' Roll Swindle [film], Black Athletes, Burnt Offering; Ruthie's Inn; 2618 San Pablo Ave. Berkeley, CA; 1983-04-22; 8.5x11.
    13. Black Dolls, Lifers, Fade To Black, Men In Black; On Broadway; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1983-04-08; 8.5x11.
    14. Hanging Party, Boss Hoss, Code Of The West, G.T. Jesus & The Crawling; [Capp Street Center]; 362 Capp St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-19; 8.5x11.
  - Folder 12, 1984- 1986 (Box 2)
    1. The Witnesses, Boss Hoss; Graffiti; 853 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-02-05; 8.5x11.
    2. Bob Scott; Sound of Music; 162 Turk St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-08-29; 8.5x11.
    3. BOB, Paris Working, Big Race; On Broadway; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; May 19; 8.5x11.
    4. Boss Hoss, The Afflicted, The Vicelords; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-25; 8.5x11.
    5. Blue Stucco; Ashkenaz; 1317 San Pablo Ave. Berkeley, CA; Thurs. [illeg.]; 8.5x11.
    6. Blood, Sweat & Steel Toes, Flexx, Bob's Shoe; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-25; 7.5x11.
    7. Boss Hoss, Slovenly; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-13; 8.5x11.
    8. Burning Witches, Earwaves, Spinster Raytime; Sound of Music; 162 Turk St. San Francisco, CA; December 8; 8.5x11.
    9. Johnny Nitro & The Doorslammers, Rude Mood, Boss Hoss; Sound of Music; 162 Turk St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-06-30, 8.5x11.
    10. Blackouts, Rank And File; [I-Beam]; [San Francisco], [CA]; 1984-11-19; 8.5x11.
    11. Music By Members of Big City, Mapenzi, Zulu Spear, & The Looters; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-11-14; 8.5x11.
    12. Impulse F; Graffiti; 853 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-02-22; 8.5x11.
    13. Big City, Freaky Executives, Zulu Spear; Wolfgang's; 901 Columbus Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1985-02-08; 8.5x11.
    14. Behold Wyoming; The Oasis; 298 11th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-04; 8.5x11.
  - Folder 13, 1983- 1986 (Box 2)
    1. Our Lady Of Pain; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-06-25; 8.5x11.
    2. Condemned To Death, N.O.T.A., Painted Willie, Emetics; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1984-08-10; 8.5x11.
    3. Condemned To Death, Special Forces, Special Forces, Public Enema; Ruthie's Inn; 2618 San Pablo Ave. Berkeley, CA; 1984-12-15; 8.5x11.
    4. Condemned To Death, Unity Instigation, Special Forces, Blind Acceptance; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1984-08-15; 8.5x11.
    5. The Corporate Veil, Up And Proper Signal; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1983-12-03; 8.5x11.
    6. Claude Ardkin And The Holy Hell Holes; Sound of Music; 162 Turk St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-28; 8.5x11.
    7. Bardo [Bardo Productions], DJ Kevin C.; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-10-27; 8.5x11.
    8. Air Tight Garage, Altar De Fey, Tin Shadows; Sound of Music; 162 Turk St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-12-15; 8.5x11.
    9. The Angel Of Thorns; Chi Chi Club; 440 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-02-06 -- The Angel Of Thorns; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-02-22; 8.5x11.
    10. American Music Club; Graffiti; 853 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-08-03; 8.5x11.
    11. Ape Cult; Ruthie's Inn; 2618 San Pablo Ave. Berkeley, CA; 1984-08-03; 8.5x11.
    12. Club Foot Orchestra, Davenports, 7 Dutch Poets, Calico Basket [That Insane Calico Basket]; 18 Sycamore St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-25; 8.5x11.
    13. Iconoclast, A State of Mind, M.J.B., Tyranny Of Structure, Group Rhythm Therapy; Club Foot; 2520 3rd St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-07-13; 8.5x11.
    14. Hydro-Matics, Ulterior Motives, Chaos; Full Moon Saloon; 1725 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-21; 8.5x11.
  - Folder 14, 1983- 1986 (Box 2)
    1. 84 Rooms, Whiskey Worms; Hotel Utah; 584 4th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-03; 8.5x11.
    2. [amateurish sketch of 3 figures with partial address stamp: Lee Batdorf in Cleveland]; 8.5x11.
    3. False Positive #1, $2; Out-of-Kontrol Data Corporation; 55 Sutter St. #487 San Francisco, CA; 8.5x11.
    4. The Urban Landscape. Videotapes/Static Work [several artists]; Artists' Television Access (ATA); 220 8th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-10; 8.5x11.
    5. Chuck Z in The Neurotic Distortion Show; The Lab; 1805 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; December 14, 15; 8.5x11.
    6. Jamming The Controls. DJs Ras Shango & T.A.O.; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 8.5x11.
    7. Altar De Fey; Graffiti; 853 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; January 15; 8.5x11.
    8. Until December; The Oasis; 298 11th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-05-08; 8.5x11.
    9. Altar De Fey, Our Lady Of Pain, Dangerous Visions; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; August 9; 8.5x11.
    10. The Funniest Hour. Starring Rick Mills, Dexter Devoe; 2140 Club; 2140 Market St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-12-17; 8.5x11.
    11. Sex Ban Hearing to Expand The Bath House Sex Ban to Private Rooms & Allow Private Spy Testimony. Picket City Hall Polk St. Steps, 8:30 am. Demand your Own Privacy, Informed Consent and Body Back From Disinforming, Scapegoating Hysterics; City Hall; 1 Dr. Carlton B. Goodlett Pl. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-24; 8.5x11.
    12. TSOL; San Francisco State. Student Union. Barbary Coast; 1650 Holloway Ave. San Francisco, CA; April 4; 8.5x11.
    13. Stir Ups, Reggie And The Rebels, Swinging Possums; On Broadway; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1983-04-03; 8.5x11.
    14. Unruly World, Keith Hennessy (3 Dogs In Underwear), Mary Reid, Susan Roebuck & Betsy Roebuck, Christine Carraher's Nth Regiment, Slick Ric, Fire In The Lake Collective; Capp Street Center; 362 Capp St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-02-08; 8.5x11.
  - Folder 15, 1984- 1986 (Box 2)
    1. Lujan's Natural Frozen Yogurt; 206 Fillmore St.; San Francisco, CA; 8.5x11.
    2. Bare Chest. Choose Mr. September. Arena.; San Francisco, CA; 1984-08-09; 8.5x11.
    3. Moving Sale! [etc.]; 903 Pine St. San Francisco, CA; 8.5x11.
    4. Paranoid Blue, Pleasant Day, Schrödinger's Cat, Heru-Ra-Ha; Club Foot; 2520 3rd St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-12; 8.5x11.
    5. Dead Beat Magazine. Calling All You Writers [etc.]; P.O. Box 590889 Golden Gate Station San Francisco, CA; 8.5x11.
    6. Strung Out? 21-Day Outpatient Methadone Detoxification [etc.]; San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-13; 8.5x11.
    7. Uh-Oh, Next To Nothing [Nexta Nothin]; Full Moon Saloon; 1725 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-01; 8.5x11.
    8. Until December; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-01; 8.5x11.
    9. My Sin; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-12-21 -- My Sin; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-12-14; 8.5x11.
    10. Paranoid Blue, M.J.B., Brain Rust, 23 Screams; Club Foot; 2520 3rd St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-06-28; 8.5x11.
    11. About Africa No.2; Bannam Place; 50a Bannam Alley; San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-10; 8.5x11.
    12. Not Home; Bannam Place; 50a Bannam Alley San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-31; 8.5x11.
    13. DD Downer, Science Project; On Broadway; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; December 6; 8.5x11.
  - Folder 16, 1983- 1986 (Box 2)
    1. Dancing. Burnt; 8.5x11.
    2. Star Wars. The Final Frontier. Blockade Livermore; Livermore, CA; 1983-09-24; 8.5x11.
    3. Peeping Tom, Black Narcissus; San Francisco Art Institute; 800 Chestnut St. San Francisco, CA; July 28; 8.5x11.
    4. He Lies! Stop The Invasion Of Nicaragua; 8.5x11.
    5. Glorious Din, Shiva Dancing, Nimbus; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-11; 8.5x11.
    6. Gone World; The Wayouts, The Cat Heads; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; October 17; 8.5x11.
    7. Game Theory, Angst, Flying Color; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-13; 8.5x11.
    8. Ha Ha; Chi Chi Club; 440 Broadway San Francisco, CA; December 6; 8.5x11.
    9. The Generics; Last Day Saloon; 406 Clement St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-20; 8.5x11.
    10. Crawl Away Machine; Berkeley Square; 1333 University Ave. 1333 University Ave. Berkeley, CA; February 20 -- Crawl Away Machine; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; February 17 -- Crawl Away Machine; Chi Chi Club; 440 Broadway San Francisco, CA; March 2; 8.5x11.
    11. Jeff Call Timothy [photos of skater]; 8.5x11.
    12. Change Orbits; April 1; 8.5x11.
  - Folder 17, 1984- 1986 (Box 2)
    1. Ugly Stick, The Muskrats; Sound Of Music; 162 Turk St. San Francisco, CA; August 24; 8.5x11.
    2. Club Foot Orchestra; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA;1985-01-27; 8.5x11.
    3. Blood, Sweat & Steel Toes, Victim's Family, Limbo Branches; On Broadway [Rock On Broadway]; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; April 4; 8.5x11.
    4. The Witnesses, Burning Witches, Butcher Boys; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; December 22; 8.5x11.
    5. County Line; Rainbow Cattle Company; 16220 Main St. Guerneville, CA; 1986-04-13; 8.5x11.
    6. [calendar]; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; April 30-May 4 -- [calendar]; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; Wed. May 7 - Sun. May 11; 8.5x11.
    7. [calendar]; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; Thurs. May 15 - Sat. May 17; 8.5x11.
    8. Detox, Tales Of Terror, Touch Me Hooker featuring Paul Castille, Blood Atonement; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-28; 8.5x11.
    9. Mordred, Sacrilege, Ass Ass Ins; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-06-08; 8.5x11.
    10. Mordred, Damage, Annex; On Broadway [Rock On Broadway]; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-04-22; 8.5x11. 11. The Blenders; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1984-01-28; 8.5x11.
    12. The Fibonaccis, The Hesitations (Berlin), Debora Iyall; Club Foot; 2520 3rd St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-04-26; 8.5x11.
    134. Housecoat Project, Frightwig; Sound Of Music; 162 Turk St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-02-08; 8.5x11.
  - Folder 18, 1983- 1986 (Box 2)
    1. Negative Raccoon Effect, Top Jimmy and the Rhythm Pigs; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-06-27; 8.5x11.
    2. The Adolescents, Wasted Youth, The Mentors, D.I.; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1985-05-17; 8.5x11.
    3. Lambsbread, The Dicks, Treason; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1984-09-21; 8.5x11.
    4. Tex & The Horseheads, Housecoat Project, Party Drivers; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-09-27; 8.5x11.
    5. Tex & The Horseheads, Housecoat Project, Party Drivers; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-09-27; 8.5x11.
    6. 7 Seconds, Christ On Parade, Verbal Abuse; Hungarian Center; 1052 Geary Blvd. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-25; 8.5x11.
    7. Anti-Nowhere League; On Broadway; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1983-07-08 -- Bad Brains; On Broadway; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1983-07-21 -- Gun Club; On Broadway; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1983-07-23; 8.5x11.
    8. Faith No More, 7 Dutch Poets, Usual Suspects, Dot Three; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-02-20; 8.5x11.
    9. Kommunity FK, Faith No More, Glorious Din, Paranoid Blue; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; Sun. 17; 8.5x11.
    10. Excel, Cryptic Slaughter, Violent Coercion, Clown Alley, Chronic Plague; New Method Warehouse; 3623 Adeline St. Emeryville, CA; 1985-12-20; 8.5x11.
    11. Bl'ast, Uniform Choice, Mock; On Broadway; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-05; 8.5x11.
    12. Chromatics; Club 181; 181 Eddy St. San Francisco, CA; 1983-12-09; 8.5x11.
    13. D.R.I., Death Angel, Sacrilege; On Broadway [Rock On Broadway]; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; March 15; 8.5x11.
  - Folder 19, 1986 (Box 2)
    1. R.K.L., Rhythm Pigs, Caustic Notions, Crash n' Burn; New Method Warehouse; 3623 Adeline St. Emeryville, CA; 1986-02-08; 8.5x11.
    2. R.K.L., Noize Boyz, Test Subjects; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-02-11; 8.5x11.
    3. R.K.L., Test Subjects, Short Dogs Grow, Giddy Up, MongrelX10; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-11; 8.5x11.
    4. R.K.L., Crash n' Burn, Miserable Sex, Neurosis; Club Foot; 2520 3rd St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-18; 8.5x11.
    5. R.K.L., Desecration, Genocide, Black Death, Vomit; Ruthie's Inn; 2618 San Pablo Ave. Berkeley, CA; 1986-02-21; 8.5x11.
    6. R.K.L., 7 Seconds; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-27 -- R.K.L.; Club Foot; 2520 3rd St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-20 -- R.K.L., Attitude Adjustment, Christ On Parade; On Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-18; 8.5x11.
    7. Echo & The Bunnymen, The Fleshtones; Berkeley Community Theatre; 1900 Allston Way Berkeley, CA; 1984-09-07; 8.5x11.
    8. Camper Van Beethoven, Victim's Family, Butthole Surfers; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-18; 8.5x11.
    9. Camper Van Beethoven, Victim's Family, Butthole Surfers; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-18; 8.5x11.
    10. Soul Asylum; Berkeley Square; 1333 University Ave. Berkeley, CA; 1986-04-08 -- Soul Asylum; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-07 -- Soul Asylum; Rough Trade; 326 6th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-06; 8.5x11.
    11. The Dicks, The Witnesses, Housecoat Project, A Few Chairs; On Broadway; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-09-06; 8.5x11.
    12. Redd Kross, Hanging Party, Shiva Dancing [Siva Dancing], Flying Colour; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-22; 8.5x11.
    13. Youth Brigade, America's Hardcore, Secret Hate, Crude; Valencia Tool & Die; 974 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; April 8; 8.5x11.
    14. Victim's Family, Caroliner Rainbow Benza Passover, Snotgreen Sea (X-member of Sleeping Dogs & Too Many Zombies), Babysitters From Hell; Club Foot; 2520 3rd St. San Francisco, CA; December 7; 8.5x11.
  - Folder 20, 1983- 1986 (Box 2)
    1. 7 Seconds, Social Unrest, Verbal Abuse, R.K.L., Doggy Style; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-27; 8.5x11.
    2. Ha Ha; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-30; 8.5x11.
    3. U.K. Subs, Exploited, The Witnesses; The Stone; 412 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-05-08; 8.5x11.
    4. X-Tal, Brain Rust, Beat Happening, M.J.B. [Mint Julep Ballet], Glorious Din; Club Foot; 2520 3rd St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-03-22; 8.5x11.
    5. Sacrilege, Death (From Florida), Desecration, Insanity; Ruthie's Inn; 2618 San Pablo Ave. Berkeley, CA; 1985-10-19; 8.5x11.
    6. M.D.C., Burnt Offering, The Dicks, Sluglords, The Afflicted, [& Special Out-Of-Town Guest]; On Broadway; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1983-04-11; 8.5x11.
    7. [calendar]; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; Mon. August 20-Fri. November 2 1984; 8.5x11.
    8. The Feelies; The Oasis; 298 11th St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-09-26; 8.5x11.
    9. D.R.I., Tyrannicide, Any Three Initials [A3I]; On Broadway; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-11 -- D.R.I., Social Unrest, Christ On Parade; On Broadway; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-11; 8.5x11.
    10. Helios Creed; Graffiti; 853 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-01-14; 8.5x11.
    11. Helios Creed; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-16; 8.5x11.
    12. Helios Creed, Short Dogs Grow, Half Blind; Hotel Utah; 584 4th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-25; 8.5x11.
    13. Helios Creed; On Broadway; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; Sat. 28; 8.5x11.
  - Folder 21, 1984- 1986 (Box 2)
    1. Johnny Thunders, Live Nude, Snail; On Broadway; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-01; 8.5x11.
    2. Flipper, Frightwig, Detox; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1984-11-30; 8.5x11.
    3. Diamanda Galas; New Performance Gallery; 3153 17th St. San Francisco, CA; May 9, 11, 13; 8.5x11.
    4. Corrosion Of Conformity, Possessed, Bl'ast, Morally Bankrupt, Capt. Crunch; Ruthie's Inn; 2618 San Pablo Ave. Berkeley, CA; 1985-02-01; 8.5x11.
    5. D.R.I., No Mercy, Stone Vengeance, Tyrannicide, Forbidden Evil; Ruthie's Inn; 2618 San Pablo Ave. Berkeley, CA; 1986-05-02; 8.5x11.
    6. D.R.I., Death Angel, Sacrilege; On Broadway [Rock On Broadway]; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 8.5x11.
    7. The Pied Piper, The Phantom; Boldwin Ct. Center; [unknown]; 1984-08-04; 8.5x11.
  - Folder 22, 1989 (Box 2)
    1. Rena And Her Men; 7th Street Entry; Minneapolis, MN; 1989-07-25; 8.5x11.
    2. The Blue Hippo, Mind Meld, Nova Mob, Leatherwood; The Cabooze; 917 Cedar Minneapolis, MN; 1989-08-05; 8.5x11.
    3. Fit To Be; 7th Street Entry; Minneapolis, MN; 1989-08-15; 8.5x11.
    4. Die Young; Roxy Music Café; Minneapolis, MN; 1989-08-02; 8.5x11.
    5. Psycheteria. Off-Your-Body Dance; First Avenue; Minneapolis, MN; 1989-08-02; 8.5x11.
    6. The Mighty Mofos, Strapping Daddy, Skeleton Ed; The Uptown; Minneapolis, MN; 1989-08-05; 8.5x11.
    7. The Skeletones; The Uptown; Minneapolis, MN; 1989-08-14; 8.5x11.
  - Folder 1, 1982- 1985 (Box 3)
    1. Musikcamp; Graffiti; 853 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-05-08; 8.5x11.
    2. Zipgun; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1982-11-11; 8.5x11.5.
    3. Primus; Graffiti; 853 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-03-21; 8.5x17.
    4. The Dicks, D.R.I., The Morlocks, Sea Hags, The Weasels, Jungle Studs; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-23 -- Dead Kennedys; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-29 -- Black Flag, S.W.A.; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-30; 8.5x17.
    5. The Dicks, D.R.I., The Morlocks, Sea Hags, The Weasels, Jungle Studs; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-23 -- Dead Kennedys, Polkacide; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-29 -- Black Flag, S.W.A.; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-30; 8.5x17.
    6. Club Foot Orchestra; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-08; 8.5x17.
    7. Club Foot Orchestra, Polkacide; Chi Chi Club; 440 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-03-23; 8.5x17.
    8. D.O.A., Conflict, Christ On Parade, The Witnesses; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-05; 8.5x17.
    9. Bike Boy; Castro Theatre; 429 Castro St. San Francisco, CA; 1983-04-30; 8.5x17.
    10. Verbal Abuse, Tales Of Terror, The Boneless Ones; On Broadway [Rock On Broadway]; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-10; 8.5x17.
    11. The Dead Milkmen, Faith No More, Glorious Din; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-02-08; 8.5x17.
    12. Black Flag, Code Of Honor, Meat Puppets, The Dicks, Los Olvidados, The Sluts, The Stains, Suicidal Tendencies, St. Vidas Dance; Aquatic Park; 3rd St. & Bancroft Way Berkeley, CA; 1983-07-16; 8.5x17.
    13. Richard Talvera, Dominique, Slick Ric, Paul Kwan, Q.R. Hand, Rene Yanez, Marshall Weber; The Lab; 1805 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-10; 8.5x17.
    14. Dead Kennedys; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-10-18; 8.5x17.
    15. T.S.O.L., Soldiers Of Fortune, Sea Hags, Levi Dextor & The Daggers; On Broadway; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-24; 8.5x17.
  - Folder 2, 1984- 1986 (Box 3)
    1. Hodel's Public Hearing On Offshore Drilling; Cathedral Hill Hotel; 1101 Van Ness Ave. San Francisco, CA; April 8; 8.5x17.
    2. Divine; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-02-05; 8.5x17.
    3. Husker Du; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-12-17 -- Frightwig, Big Race; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-12-18; 8.5x17.
    4. Wall Of Voodoo, Pray For Rain; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-30 -- Knitters; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-06; 8.5x17.
    5. The Minutemen, Slovenly; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-09-23 -- The Lucy Show; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-09-30 -- Poison Girls, Beat Rodeo; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-10-07; 8.5x17.
    6. Chris Isaak, The Naked Into; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-07-08 -- The Vipers (from N.Y.); I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-07-15; 8.5x17.
    7. Big Race; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-12-18 -- Red Hot Chili Peppers; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-01-07; 8.5x17.
    8. The Fleshtones, Zeitgeist; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-26 -- Voice Farm; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-09-02 -- Jeffrey Lee Pierce; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-09-16; 8.5x17.
    9. The Three Johns, The Flaming Lips; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-05 -- Until December, Bolshoi; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-12; 8.5x17.
    10. The Ventures, Flying Color; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-04-22 -- Bonnie Hayes; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-04-29 -- The Bongos; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-05-06; 8.5x17.
    11. Rank and File, Blackouts; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-11-19 -- Snakefinger; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-11-27 -- Hoodoo Gurus; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-12-03 -- Let's Active; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-12-10; 8.5x17.
    12. 10,000 Maniacs, Camper Van Beethoven; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-14 -- Gene Loves Jezebel; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-21; 8.5x17.
    13. The Morlocks, 28th Day, Thin White Rope; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-02 -- The Replacements; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-09; 8.5x17.
  - Folder 3, 1984- 1986 (Box 3)
    1. Return Of The Great Dollar Dance; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-01; 8.5x17.
    2. 54-40, T.S.O.L.; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-08-13 -- The Ventures; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-08-20 -- The Lyres; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-08-27; 8.5x17.
    3. Sugar Minott; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-08-06 -- The Cult, Bunnydrums; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-07-30 -- 54-40; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-08-13; 8.5x17.
    4. The Golden Palominos, Eddie Ray Porter (formerly State Of Things); I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-24 -- Butthole Surfers; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-31; 8.5x17.